Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
- Landscape Architecture Drawings, / Date(s): ca. 1941 - ca. 1995; 0000; / Quantity: ca. 483 tubes; 128 folders; 2 boxes / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - New Haven Parks / Lighthouse Point Park, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0684; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: <112x96cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in mixed media related to this coastal municipal property.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #773, "New Haven Parks ... Parking lot."
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #681, #682, #686.
  - New Haven Parks / West Rock Park, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0686; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <162x1907cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans, including Master Plan, for the municipal park at West Rock.
    Note: The rock itself best known as cavern hideout for three regicide judges who fled to America following the restoration of Charles II.
    Location of associated materials: Cf.#681, #682, #684.
  - Southwest Washington Schools / William Syphax School, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0689; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <110x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and prints of site.
    Note: Built in 1902 in honor of African-American educator William Syphax, the school has subsequently been redeveloped as condominiums.
  - Southwest Washington Schools/ Bowen Elementary School, / Date(s): 1966 - 1967; Tube: 0690; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <111x109cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and annotated prints related to this project.
  - Tenth Street Overlook, / Date(s): 1966 - 1967; Tube: 0691; / Quantity: 76 / Dimensions: <170x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original materials and prints related to this ambitious plan focused on an important Washington area.
    Scale: Varies,.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ..., pp.68-69.
  - Tufts University, / Date(s): 1967 - 1969; Tube: 0692; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <136x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and annotated prints produced over a two-year period.
  - University of Chicago/Regenstein Library/Fermi Memorial, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0693; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: <133x86cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary landscape plans, together with prints of architectural drawings.
  - University of Lagos, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0694; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: 105x74cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary planting plan and schematic drawings in mixed media.
  - University of Vermont / Parking and Traffic, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0701; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <108x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints; the Parking and Traffic studies were among several projects undertaken for the UV at this time.
  - University of Vermont / Ski Area, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0702; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: <169x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints.
    Note: In 2006, the UV ski areas were located at Stowe: at the Stowe Mountain Resort and the Trapp Family Lodge. Both sites have other Kiley connections.
  - Ansul Chemical Company, / Date(s): 1966 - 1967; Tube: 0705; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <119x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans (in mixed media) related to Parking Facility and "Functional Services Center".
    Note: Now a division of Tyco Industries, the headquarters for Ansul, a manufacturer of fire-fighting supplies, was designed by the Chicago firm of C.F. Murphy.
    Note: Murphy and Kiley collaborated on other jobs; most notably the Chicago Filtration Plant.
  - Concordia College, / Date(s): 1964 - 1966; Tube: 0707; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <107x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Kiley drawings in mixed media, related to re-vamping of campus plan. File includes original plan from Saarinen office.
    Published in: "A Village Design for a College Campus",Progressive Architecture, December 1958, 39:12, pp. 88-101.
  - Wolf Trap Foundation for Performing Arts, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0709; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <183x109cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Site plans and renderings in mixed media.
  - Sir Winston Churchill Square, / Date(s): 1966 - 1976; Tube: 0714; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: <107x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Kiley project list indicates this was both a landscape and architecture job.
    Note: Churchill Square is an important public gathering space in downtown Edmonton.
  - Drake University Master Plan, / Date(s): 197-?; Tube: 0715; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <60"x44" / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes aerial photographs, general site plans and planting plans for dining hall and dormitory area.
  - Minnesota Institute of Arts, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0716; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <155x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Identified as a landscape job, the file contains only land surveys.
    Note: The museum building was designed by Mead, McKim & White (1915); subsequent renovations were made by by Kenzo Tange (1974) and Michael Graves (2006).
  - Chicago Inland Regional Parks Study, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0717; / Quantity: 78 / Dimensions: <184x117cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes analytic drawings, schematic plans and diagrams for three parks and suggested "Recreational and Cultural Activities" for 21 wards.
  - United States Air Force Academy II, / Date(s): 1967 - 1968; Tube: 0718; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: 107 x 76cm. / Medium: Diazotypes / Support: Acetate film
    Note: Includes two drawings set; all dated 1968.
    Location of associated materials: See also: File #415 for earlier work dating from 1956-1957.
    Published in: Cf. citations which accompany entry for file #415.
  - Cummins Engine Company / Fleetguard Expansion, / Date(s): 1967 - 1974; Tube: 0719; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <108x118cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mylar (TM)
    Note: File includes site plans only, dated 1974.
  - Cummins Engine Company / Warehouse, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0720; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 110x92cm. / Medium: Ink; pencil / Support: Tracing vellum
    Scale: 1"=60'.
    Location of associated materials: See also #5000, Cummins Engine Company General Office Building.
  - New Haven Parks / Fort Hale and East Shore Park, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0721; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <242x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes site plans and preliminary drawings related to these civic parks on New Haven Harbor.
    Location of associated materials: See also; #681 "New Have Parks...East Shore" and #1025 "East Shore Park -- Phase II."
  - Rock Valley College, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0722; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <124x99cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Ink, pencil and marker on diazo prints and vellum.
  - New Haven Parks / Lighthouse/Bathhouse, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0723; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: 109x82cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Material related to sites of two New Haven Harbor lighthouses.
    Location of associated materials: See also #684 "New Haven Parks -- Lighthouse Point."
  - University of Wisconsin / South Lower Campus, / Date(s): 1967 - 1968; Tube: 0724; / Quantity: 19 / Dimensions: <133x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes original drawings and annotated prints, dated 1967-1968.
  - New Haven Parks / Wooster Street Playground, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0725; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <100x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Maps, prints and drawings in a variety of media.
  - New Haven Parks / Lenzi Playground, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0726; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <100x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Prints and drawings in a variety of media.
  - State University of New York at Potsdam / S-6, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0729; / Quantity: 22 / Dimensions: <108x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Scale: Not indicated.
    Location of associated materials: See also #5027 and #0555.
  - Franklin Park Zoo, / Date(s): 1885 - 1967; Tube: 0730; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 115x91cm. / Medium: Stats (copy) / Support: Paper
    Note: Repro of original 1885 Olmsted plan of Franklin Park; to be used in one of several master plan studies of the zoo undertaken in the 1950s and 1960s.
    Note: This project was undertaken with the Boston firm Perry ..., now Perry Dean Rogers.
    Scale: ca. 1:2,700
  - Marcus Center for the Performing Arts, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0733; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <107x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in mixed media; bluelines annotated from site visit.
    Location of associated materials: See also: #661, "Milwaukee Center for the Performing Arts", center's prior name.
  - Southwest Urban Renewal Project, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0734; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <110x80cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Paper
    Note: Plans in a variety of media; related to one of many Harry Weese architectural and planning initiatives in Washington in the 1950s and 1960s.
  - Stowe Ski Development, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0735; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <65x63cm. / Medium: Felt-tip pen / Support: Vellum
    Note: No indication of origin in ODK.
  - Calgary Place, / Date(s): 1967 - 1968; Tube: 0738; / Quantity: 202 / Dimensions: <110x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Substantial file of architectural and landscape materials dealing with the development of the Calgary Place site.
    Note: Includes material related to the Tower and shopping mall.
    Note: The Calgary Tower (originally The Husky Tower) was briefly the tallest structure in Canada.
    Published in: Cf. THE COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 211.
  - Tufts University / Eaton Hall, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0741; / Quantity: 26 / Dimensions: <121x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes material in mixed media and format. Built in 1908, Eaton Hall is now the Tufts Computing Center.
  - FBI Headquarters, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0744; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 107x62cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Solitary item, labelled "Proposed Tree Planting in Front of F.B.I."
    Note: Approved for construction in 1952; a variety of delays, the final group of employees did not move into the building until 1977.
    Scale: 1/16"=1'0".
  - New Haven Parks / East Rock Park, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0746; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <222x107cm. / Medium: Diazotype prints / Support: Polyester film
    Note: Master plan drawing with composite perspective views.
    Note: East Rock Park is both the oldest and largest in the New Haven system.
  - Killington Ski Area Expansion, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0747; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: <191x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Perspective drawings in mixed media.
  - Mulberry Square, / Date(s): 1966 - 1967; Tube: 0753; / Quantity: 25 / Dimensions: <110x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in a variety of media.
  - University of California/Santa Cruz, / Date(s): 1967 - 1969; Tube: 0754; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <112x70cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary and working drawings related to Santa Cruz/Kresge College site.
  - Williams College, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0757; / Quantity: 48 / Dimensions: <107x148cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes drawings for "WIlliams College Library."
    Note: The "Williams College Library" is included as Job #801 in the Master List of the ODK; no separate file exists in the archive.
  - State University of New York at Potsdam, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0759; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <114x74cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings for updated Master Plan for this SUNY campus.
  - Pacific Petroleums / Pacific 66 Plaza, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0766; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <108x79cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans related to this corporate/public space.
  - Carleton College / Phase I, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0770; / Quantity: 28 / Dimensions: <130x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Background materials and plans related to the Carleton campus.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #673, "Carleton College".
  - New Haven Parks / Lighthouse Point Park/ Parking Lot, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0773; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 114x88cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Site plans for park parking lot.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #684. "New Haven Parks/Lighthouse Point Park".
  - Tufts University / President's House, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0775; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <107x74cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Landscape plans for the President's residence; one of several jobs undertaken on the Tufts campus during this period.
  - Tufts University / New Women's Residence Hall, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0788; / Quantity: 26 / Dimensions: <108x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes prints and drawings on trace.
  - University of Vermont / Medical Building, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0795; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <108x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints and plans.
  - New Haven Parks / Grand Avenue, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0800; / Quantity: 25 / Dimensions: <96x64cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Substantial file related to bathhouse and grounds.
  - University of Vermont / Medical Center Hospital, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 0803; / Dimensions: <94x63cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Diazotype prints
    Note: Plans, including land and building surveys, for the former Mary Fletcher Hospital, renamed in 1967 as the Medical Center Hospital.
    Note: The Medical Center Hospital is a teaching hospital affiliated with the University of Vermont.
  - Sanders Residence, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0805; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <116x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Ink, pencil, zip-a-tone on trace and vellum.
  - Wadsworth Atheneum Garden, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0806; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <89x96cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Includes axonometric view of site,
  - University of Vermont / Allied Medical Health Building, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0807; / Quantity: 59 / Dimensions: <108x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Identified as master plan component for University of Vermont School of Medicine.
  - Sinness Residence, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0809; / Quantity: items / Dimensions: 3 / Medium: Ink; pencil / Support: Sepia prints
    Note: Annotated site plan, sections and perspectives.,
  - Mt. Washington Summit Development, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0811; / Quantity: 23 / Dimensions: <122x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Includes various media and support materials
    Published in: Cf. the COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 212 for a brief presentation of this commission.
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0812; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <134x91cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and prints related to the CMA grounds; laid out originally by the Olmsted Brothers. The original structure by Hubbell & Benes (1916) was enlarged by Breuer in 1970-1971.
  - Xerox Corporation / Rochester, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0814; / Quantity: 47 / Dimensions: <151x90cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes materials in a mixture of media and supports.
  - Floating City, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0816; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <119x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Conceptual plans and drawings for a proposed mixed-use development to be built on a "mandala" composed of canals and earthworks.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 211.
  - Williams Residence, / Date(s): 1968 - 1969; Tube: 0817; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: <107x68cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Drawings bear title "Alterations to a vacation cottage for Dr. William H. Button", tho' Williams identified as client elsewhere.
  - Grandfather Golf & Country Club, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0818; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <204x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Site and survey plans, in mixed media, for plan of this residential golfing resort.
  - New York Zoological Park [ Bronx Zoo], / Date(s): 1943 - 1968; Tube: 0819; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 193x93cm. / Medium: Diazo print / Support: Paper
    Note: File contains only the 1943 topo survey; project cited in the COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 212, with Ketchum noted as architect.
  - Michelin Tire Corporation, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0820; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <132x80cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes mixed media drawings from ODK, together with prints of architectural drawings.
  - BOK Motor Bank, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0821; / Quantity: 29 / Dimensions: <147x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes blueline prints and mixed media on vellum.
    Scale: Mixed.
  - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art / Cornell University, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0825; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <108x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes set of architect's schematics.
  - Mount Waumbeck, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0827; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <108x187cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes, topos, preliminary drawings and prints.
  - Philadelphia Child Guidance Clinic, / Date(s): 1968 - 1970; Tube: 0831; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <209x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes drawings and prints.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #835, Philadelphia's Children's Hospital.
  - Knowles Residence, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0836; / Quantity: 145 / Dimensions: <141x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Griswold Residence, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0837; / Quantity: 18 / Dimensions: <137x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary architectural drawings and landscape working drawings.
  - State University of New York at Buffalo/ Campus Plan/ Science Center, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0839; / Quantity: 55 / Dimensions: <115x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans related to proposed multi-disciplinary (Science, Law and Administration) complex designed by Weese for the SUNY/Buffalo site.
    Note: Identified as related to Science Center.
  - State University of New York at Buffalo/ Law& Administration Center, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0840; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <109x84cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings related to O'Brian Hall on the SUNY campus.
    Scale: 1"=32'.
    Published in: Cf. the special "Weese" issue of Process Architecture, November 1979.
  - Cannon Pool, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0842; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: <135x46cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes preliminary drawings; client identification tentative.
  - Dallas/Fort Worth International Airport, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0843; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <290x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes preliminary studies.
  - Guilford (ME) Town Plan, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0845; / Quantity: 19 / Dimensions: <113x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes maps and drawings.
  - Hanover College, / Date(s): 1964 - 1970; Tube: 0847; / Quantity: 35 / Dimensions: <108x148cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings file dates from mid-60s: the Hanover campus exceeded 500 acres in size at that time.
    Note: Much of the campus landscape was destroyed by a tornado in 1974; there has been significant restoration of the grounds.
  - Hopkins Housing / Williamstown, MA, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0848; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: 107x81cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Site plans and drawings; related to Kiley planning assignments at Williams College during this period?
    Note: The Hopkins Farm and forest preserve complex are Williams College properties.
    Note: Identified as "Hopkins Farm" on plans.
  - International Civil Aviation Organization Headquarters, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0849; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: 70x109cm. / Medium: Ink / Support: Polyester film
    Note: The ICAO, a United Nations body, is now based in the Quarter International of Montreal.
  - Laird Properties, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0850; / Quantity: 40 / Dimensions: <203x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Topographic surveys and analysis drawings related to property owned by this limited partnership.
  - New Haven Rowing Channel, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0852; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 107x116cm. / Medium: ? / Support: Polyester film
    Note: Rendering in an unknown medium on polyester film.
    Scale: Unscaled.
  - YWCA of Minneapolis, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0853; / Quantity: 23 / Dimensions: <108x100cm. / Medium: Mixed Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in a variety of media; the Y building which stood at 1130 Nicollet Ave.in this period was demolished in 1974.
    Note: A new building was erected on the original site.
  - Multiple Use Feasibility Study / Washington, D.C., / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0854; / Quantity: 56 / Dimensions: <124x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: During the 1960s, Weese was involved in a variety of projects in the capital, including the South-West Master Plan and several housing schemes.
    Note: File includes prints and original materials in mixed media.
  - Ross Residence, / Date(s): 1969 - 1970; Tube: 0856; / Quantity: 70 / Dimensions: <107x70cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings dating from a variety of periods in the design process.
  - Snowmass at Aspen, / Date(s): 1969 - 1970; Tube: 0858; / Quantity: 39 / Dimensions: <159x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings file related to planning at Snowmass.
  - Squibb-Beech-nut, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0860; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <107x84cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings file related to landscape plan for Lawrenceville facility. Original client now Bristol-Myers Squibb.
    Note: HOK has since further developed this headquarters site.
  - Tufts University, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0861; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <108x232cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes several ODK projects at Tufts; work focused on central campus, parking and traffic.
  - Franconia College, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0863; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <108x128cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes only topos.
    Note: Franconia College was in operation 1963-1977.
  - Random Farms, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0864; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <157x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes annotated prints in various media.
    Note: Unclear whether Mt. Kisco or Chappaqua; (property aparently spanned both towns originally).
  - Wildcat Mountain, / Date(s): 1969; Tube: 0865; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <92x125cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Wildcat notable as a ski area free from residential or other "development".
    Published in: Cf. THE COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 212.
  - Charlotte Nature Museum, / Date(s): 1970; Tube: 0871; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <107x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File consists only of 2 drawings, apparently to be overlaid on other (missing) plans.
  - Carrabassett Sugarloaf, / Date(s): 1970; Tube: 0872; / Quantity: 38 / Dimensions: <208x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Industrial Medical Center of Columbus, / Date(s): 1970; Tube: 0874; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <99x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings and architectural prints for the clinic adjacent to the main Cummins Engine Company plant.